Guide to the University of Montana (Missoula, Mont.) University Relations Records 1930-2012
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
- Biographical Information, 1937-1983; Series III
  - Genz, Darly Arthur, 1975; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/84)
  - Gercken, Richard L., 1971-1976; affiliation: Librarian (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/85)
  - Gilbert, Vedder M. Dr., 1959-1973; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/86)
  - Gilchrist, Raleigh Dr., 1966; affiliation: Distinguished Service Award (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/87)
  - Goldman, Ivan G., 1979; affiliation: Journalism (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/88)
  - Gordon, James, 1973-1974; affiliation: Physical Plant (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/89)
  - Gorman, Robert E., 1958-1972; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/90)
  - Gray, Bruce, 1969; affiliation: ASUM Vice President (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/91)
  - Greely, Attorney General Michael T., 1978; affiliation: Guest at Graduation (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/92)
  - Greene, Robert, 1975-1976; affiliation: Drama (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/93)
  - Greenwood, Frank Dr., 1972-1974; affiliation: Computer Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/94)
  - Griffith, Kay, 1971-1974; affiliation: Librarian (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/95)
  - Gritzner, Charles F., 1973-1975; affiliation: Geography (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/96)
  - Gulbrandsen, Norman, 1947; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/97)
  - Guthrie, Robert C., 1947; affiliation: Honorary Doctoral Degree (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/98)
  - Guy, Donald Dr., 1971; affiliation: Montana's Minuteman Education Program (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/99)
  - Hall, James Franklin Dr., 1968-1971; affiliation: Continuing Education / UM Extension (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/100)
  - Hall, Joanne, 1973-1974; affiliation: Home Economics (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/101)
  - Halligan, Michael, 1974-1975; affiliation: Student Affairs (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/102)
  - Halpin, W. Gerald, 1973; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/103)
  - Halvorson, Curtis H., ca. 1968; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/104)
  - Hansen, Bert Dr., 1951-1964; affiliation: History (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/105)
  - Hardey, Mabelle G., 1966-1973; affiliation: Sociology (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/106)
  - Hart, Jeffrey A., 1975; affiliation: Botany (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/107)
  - Harvey, Leroy H., 1956-1969; affiliation: Botany (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/108)
  - Harvey, Maria A., 1967-1972; affiliation: Spanish (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/109)
  - Harvey, Paul, 1969; affiliation: Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/110)
  - Haswell, Chief Justice Frank, 1978; affiliation: Guest at Graduation (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/111)
  - Senator Mark O. Hatfield, 1969; affiliation: Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/112)
  - Haynes, Ann Wilson, 1966; affiliation: Distinguished Service Award (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/113)
  - Heathcote, Jud, 1973-1976; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/114)
  - Helbing, Albert T. Dr., 1951-1969; affiliation: Business Administration (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/115)
  - Henderson, Greg, ca. 1977; affiliation: ASUM President (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/116)
  - Hendrickson, John Hunt, 1967-1976; affiliation: Librarian (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/117)
  - Hertler, Charles F., 1951-1972; affiliation: HPER (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/118)
  - Heywood, Lloyd A., 1973-1976; affiliation: HPER (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/119)
  - Hilger, David, 1972-1974; affiliation: Aerospace Studies (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/120)
  - David A. Hill Jr., 1976; affiliation: ASUM President (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/121)
  - Hitchcock, Leo, 1975; affiliation: Botany (Box-folder Series 3 - 2/122)
  - Hodges, Lawrence W., 1963-1972; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/1)
  - Hoffmann, Robert S. Dr., 1967-1968; affiliation: Zoology (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/2)
  - Holden, Kathleen Fleming, 1973-1977; affiliation: UM Equal Employment Opportunity Office (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/3)
  - Holland, Rupert R., 1976; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/4)
  - Hollenbaugh, William Charles, 1971-1973; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/5)
  - Holmgren, Robert, 1975; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/6)
  - Holter, William L., ca. 1972; affiliation: Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/7)
  - Honkala, Fred S. Dr, 1948-1970; affiliation: Dean of Graduate School, Director of Research, U.M. Foundation (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/8)
  - Hood, Charles E., 1966-1972; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/9)
  - Hoover, Jack L., 1970-1976; affiliation: Director of Admissions (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/10)
  - Hoover, Paul E., 1973; affiliation: UM Order of the Grizzly Award (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/11)
  - Hooper, Bruce C., 1961; affiliation: Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/12)
  - Horsky, Charles A., 1973; affiliation: UM Order of the Grizzly Award (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/13)
  - Hosford, Helga, 1975-1977; affiliation: German (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/14)
  - Hotho, Steven F., 1972-1975; affiliation: Sociology and Social Welfare (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/15)
  - Hudiburgh, Terry, 1975-1976; affiliation: Accounting (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/16)
  - Huggins, James M., 1967-1975; affiliation: UM Federal Credit Union (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/17)
  - Hummerl, J. George, 1966-1976; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/18)
  - Hunt, Henry, 1975-1976; affiliation: Gallery of Visual Arts (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/19)
  - Hunt, Lawrence J. Dr., 1966-1967; affiliation: Business Administration (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/20)
  - Huszagh, Fredrick Wickitt, 1973; affiliation: Law (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/21)
  - Inabnit, Dr. Darnell J., 1964-1966; affiliation: Executive Vice President (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/22)
  - Inch, Herbert, 1943; affiliation: Honorary Doctoral Degree (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/23)
  - Ireland, Elizabeth, 1946; affiliation: Office of Public Instruction- Office of the Superintendent (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/24)
  - Jacobseon, Frank Joel, 1973-1975; affiliation: Drama (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/25)
  - Jacobson, Garth, 1978-1979; affiliation: ASUM President (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/26)
  - Jacobson, Stephanie, 1974-1975; affiliation: Coordinator of Orientation; UM Center for Student Development (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/27)
  - Jakupcak, Michael J., 1973-1977; affiliation: Speech Pathology and Audiology (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/28)
  - Jameson, William J., 1954; affiliation: Honorary Doctoral Degree (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/29)
  - Janetos, Dimitri, 1974-1975; affiliation: Director, Campus Recreation (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/30)
  - Jennings, Carolyn A., 1974-1975; affiliation: Student Development (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/31)
  - Jennings, Joseph W. Dr., 1969-1971; affiliation: Psychology (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/32)
  - Jeppesen, Charles Rulon Dr., 1954-1973; affiliation: Physics (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/33)
  - Jerrim, John, 1976-1977; affiliation: Wrestling Coach (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/34)
  - Johnson, Dorothy M., 1953-1972; affiliation: Journalism (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/35)
  - Johnson, Agnes, 1973; affiliation: Social Work (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/36)
  - Johnson, John C., ca. 1970; affiliation: Sociology (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/37)
  - Johnson, Thomas G. Dr., 1966-1968; affiliation: Business Administration (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/38)
  - Juday, Richard E., 1947-1977; affiliation: Chemistry (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/39)
  - Judge, Governor Thomas, 1973-1976; affiliation: Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/40)
  - Kadec, Anthony, 1975; affiliation: Drama (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/41)
  - Kain, Ronald S., 1962; affiliation: Distinguished Service Award (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/42)
  - Kamego, Albert, 1976; affiliation: Chemistry (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/43)
  - Katz, Dr. Charles J., 1971-1978; affiliation: Health Service (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/44)
  - Kaul, Larry, 1974; affiliation: Personnel Assistant Director (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/45)
  - Kay, Charles E., 1977; affiliation: Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/46)
  - Kelley, Rick, 1975; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/47)
  - Kelly, Bill, 1968; affiliation: Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/48)
  - Kelly, Evans, 1976; affiliation: Upward Bound Coordinator (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/49)
  - Kelly, Katherine D., 1976; affiliation: Microbiology, Health Service (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/50)
  - Kennedy, Edward M., 1971; affiliation: U.S. Senator (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/51)
  - Kickert, Ronald N., 1974; affiliation: Botany and Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/52)
  - Kielkh, Lawrence L., ca. 1970s; affiliation: Sociology (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/53)
  - Kim, Chan-Hie, 1974; affiliation: Religious Studies (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/54)
  - Kimball, David, 1974-1976; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/55)
  - Kimpton, Lawrence A., 1948; affiliation: Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/56)
  - Kinghorn, Durnell, 1973-1976; affiliation: KUFM (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/57)
  - Kissinger, Henry A., 1974; affiliation: Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/58)
  - Kitt, Berney, 1966; affiliation: Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/59)
  - Knudsen, Gerhard M., 1968-1969; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/60)
  - Kovalchik, Janet L., 1973-1974; affiliation: Social Work (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/61)
  - Krauzer, Steven, 1975; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/62)
  - Kreisberg, Michael, ca. 1971; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/63)
  - Krier, John P., 1952-1971; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/64)
  - Hammen, Oscar J., 1947-1974; affiliation: History (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/65)
  - Kruckeberg, Robert F., ca. 1969; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/66)
  - Kuni, Lois, 1975-1977; affiliation: UM Center for Student Development (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/67)
  - Kyu Yul Lee, 1973-1974; affiliation: Computer Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/68)
  - Lackschewitz, Klaus H., 1969-1980; affiliation: Botany (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/69)
  - Lacounte, Larry, 1973-1975; affiliation: Upward Bound and Special Services (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/70)
  - Lai, Grace T., 1971; affiliation: Librarian (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/71)
  - Lai, Yuan- Zong, 1973-1975; affiliation: Forestry and Chemistry (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/72)
  - Landers, Richard E., 1975; affiliation: Montana Kaimin (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/73)
  - Landini, Richard G., 1970-1976; affiliation: Academic Vice President (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/74)
  - Langton, Russell G., 1972; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/75)
  - Langworthy, Karen, 1975-1976; affiliation: Dance (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/76)
  - Lard, Gene, 1976-1977; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/77)
  - Larsen, Hervert R., ca. 1970; affiliation: Sociology and Social Welfare (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/78)
  - Law, M. James, 1972; affiliation: Speech Pathology and Audiology (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/79)
  - Lawson, Carl D., 1974; affiliation: Aerospace Studies (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/80)
  - Lee, Andrew E., ca. 1968; affiliation: Psychology (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/81)
  - Lee, Dr. Kyu Y., 1975-1976; affiliation: Computer Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/82)
  - Lehmayer-Karlowitsch, Berta, 1971; affiliation: Foreign Languages (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/83)
  - Leitch, William, 1971-1974; affiliation: Zoology (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/84)
  - Lepage, Julien, 1972-1976; affiliation: Military Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/85)
  - Leslie, Cynthia Jane, 1973-1974; affiliation: HPER (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/86)
  - Leslie, Jody, 1971-1976; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/87)
  - Lewis, Marchel, ca. 1972; affiliation: Instructor Management (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/88)
  - Lillehaugen, Sylvia, undated; affiliation: Librarian (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/89)
  - Lindemann, Zona, 1971-1973; affiliation: HPER (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/90)
  - Longfish, George, 1972-1975; affiliation: Art (Visiting) (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/91)
  - Long, Franklin A., 1963-1970; affiliation: Honorary Doctoral Degree (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/92)
  - Longrove, Robert E., 1973; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/93)
  - Lortus, Buck, 1967-1973; affiliation: HPER (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/94)
  - Lottich, Kenneth V., 1958-1967; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/95)
  - Loughman, Michael, 1971; affiliation: Geography (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/96)
  - Loy, Myrna, 1973; affiliation: UM Order of the Grizzly Award (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/97)
  - Lucas, Robert C., 1971-1972; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/98)
  - Luetzow, Arthur E., 1973; affiliation: Chemistry (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/99)
  - Luginbuhl, Greg, 1974-1975; affiliation: Art (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/100)
  - Lundburg, Wilford, 1971-1973; affiliation: Law (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/101)
  - Lundborg, Louis B., 1973; affiliation: UM Order of the Grizzly Award (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/102)
  - Lund, Gage, 1973; affiliation: UM Order of the Grizzly Award (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/103)
  - Lundstrom, Hans, 1972-1973; affiliation: Chemistry (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/104)
  - Lusin, Mary Jo, 1976; affiliation: HPER (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/105)
  - Lyman, Cheryl, 1974-1975; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/106)
  - Lynde, Stan, 1965-1971; affiliation: Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/107)
  - Lyon, Jack L. Dr., 1971; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/108)
  - Lyons, Rusty, 1971-1973; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/109)
  - Maclean, Norman, 1981-1982; affiliation: Honorary Doctoral Degree (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/110)
  - Maclay, Harry D., 1966; affiliation: Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/111)
  - Macpherson, Thea, 1973; affiliation: Alumni, teacher (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/112)
  - Madden, Forrest G., 1973-1976; affiliation: Forestry (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/113)
  - Mahaffey, Roy Dean, 1971-1973; affiliation: Speech Communication (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/114)
  - Mahoney, John, 1975-1976; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/115)
  - Mallory, William R., 1973-1974; affiliation: Physics and Astronomy (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/116)
  - Malouf, Arline Mrs., 1970-1975; affiliation: Home Economics (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/117)
  - Manship, James D., 1971; affiliation: Military Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/118)
  - Marsillo, Lino Anthony, 1971; affiliation: Business (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/119)
  - Martell, Earl W., 1955-1974; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/120)
  - Martin, Ruby R., 1967-1972; affiliation: Foreign Languages (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/121)
  - Mertinez, Richard, 1973; affiliation: Social Work (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/122)
  - Martinson, Alvhild J., 1967-1971; affiliation: Business Administration (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/123)
  - Maslan, Peter, 1972-1973; affiliation: Drama (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/124)
  - Mason, Sudie Doughton, 1971-1975; affiliation: Home Economics (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/125)
  - Maury, Lowndes, 1946-1974; affiliation: Honorary Doctoral Degree (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/126)
  - Mayes, Bobby, 1975; affiliation: Zoology (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/127)
  - McBride, John, 1975-1976; affiliation: Geology (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/128)
  - McBride, Judy, 1971; affiliation: College of Arts and Sciences (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/129)
  - McCabe, John M., 1970-1972; affiliation: Law (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/130)
  - McCaine, James A, 1945-1968; affiliation: Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/131)
  - McCarthy, Michael M., 1973-1976; affiliation: Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/132)
  - McCloy, James M. Dr., 1969-1971; affiliation: Geography (Box-folder Series 3 - 3/133)
  - McClure, Eddye, 1976-1977; affiliation: Women's Athletics, HPER (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/1)
  - McCollum, Morris, ca. 1970; affiliation: UM Bookstore Director (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/2)
  - McCrory, John P., 1971-1973; affiliation: Law (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/3)
  - McDaniel, Donald L., 1974-1975; affiliation: Scholarships and Grants Officer (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/4)
  - McDermott, John T., 1972-1973; affiliation: Law (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/5)
  - McDonald, James, 1973; affiliation: Physical Plant (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/6)
  - McDuffie, Helen, 1973-1974; affiliation: Director of Orientation (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/7)
  - McDuffie, Keith A. Dr., 1971-1973; affiliation: Foreign Languages (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/8)
  - McFarland, Mrs. Carl, ca. 1970; affiliation: Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/9)
  - McGuire, Margaret H., 1973-1981; affiliation: Center for Student Development (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/10)
  - McIntosh, Carl W., 1971; affiliation: MSU President (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/11)
  - McKenzie, Ken, 1976; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/12)
  - McKinnon, Edna Rankin, 1974; affiliation: Honorary Doctoral Degree (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/13)
  - McKinsey, Lauren S., 1975; affiliation: Political Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/14)
  - McLeod, Walter H., 1962; affiliation: Distinguished Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/15)
  - McQuillan, Alan G., 1976; affiliation: Economics (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/16)
  - McQuiston, John H., 1976; affiliation: Sociology (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/17)
  - McWhorter, Jack, 1971; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/18)
  - Meinholtz, Peggy, 1975-1976; affiliation: Montana Repertory Theater (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/19)
  - Merriam, H.G., 1974; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/20)
  - Menier, Raymond A., 1979; affiliation: Controller (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/21)
  - Micken, Darrell J., 1971-1973; affiliation: Speech Pathology and Audiology (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/22)
  - Midgett, Adelaine S., 1957, 1978; affiliation: Librarian (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/23)
  - Midgett, Kent, 1977; affiliation: Alumni, Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/24)
  - Migid, Adel A., 1975-1977; affiliation: Drama (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/25)
  - Mihevic, Pat, 1974; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/26)
  - Miles, John A., 1974-1975; affiliation: Religion (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/27)
  - Miller, Dirk, 1975; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/28)
  - Miller, Donald Curtis, 1968-1974; affiliation: Journalism (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/29)
  - Miller, Justin, 1948, 1951, 1962; affiliation: Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/30)
  - Miller, M. Lynda, 1977-1981; affiliation: Communication Science and Disorders (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/31)
  - Minckler, Jeff Dr., 1953; affiliation: Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/32)
  - Montgomery, Wayne, 1967; affiliation: Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/33)
  - Mooney, Guy, 1966; affiliation: Journalism Award (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/34)
  - Moon, Marianne, 1973; affiliation: Social Work (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/35)
  - Moore, John E., 1948-1972; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/36)
  - Moore, William R., 1974; affiliation: Honorary Doctoral Degree (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/37)
  - Moreland, James D., 1972-1974; affiliation: Military Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/38)
  - Mosby, A.J., 1966; affiliation: Donation (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/39)
  - Mosby, Aline, 1966; affiliation: Distinguished Service Award (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/40)
  - Mosher, Naidia R., 1974-1977; affiliation: Drama (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/41)
  - Mount, John, 1973-1975; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/42)
  - Mount, Lorna, 1975; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/43)
  - Muckelston, Sandra R., 1972-1976; affiliation: Law (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/44)
  - Munro, James Jr., 1954-1971; affiliation: Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/45)
  - Nash, Laurence Jay, 1973; affiliation: Program Director, Division of Continuing Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/46)
  - Nash, Michael M., 1970; affiliation: Business Administration (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/47)
  - Nassif, S. Joseph, 1966; affiliation: Drama (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/48)
  - Nasuti, James J., 1967; affiliation: Geography (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/49)
  - Nelson, Bruce Edward, 1974; affiliation: Student Lobbyist (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/50)
  - Nelson, Conny (Dr.), 1976; affiliation: Academic Vice President Candidate (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/51)
  - Nelson, David E., 1974-1975; affiliation: Montana Arts Council Executive Director (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/52)
  - Nelson, Rita M., 1971-1972; affiliation: Librarian (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/53)
  - Nethercot, Dr. Arthur H., 1965; affiliation: Visiting Professor English (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/54)
  - Nev, Clyde W., ca. 1972; affiliation: Business (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/55)
  - Nickel, David, 1977; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/56)
  - Niethold, Edgar F., 1969; affiliation: Food Services (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/57)
  - Niles, Dr. Russell D., 1953, 1963; affiliation: Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/58)
  - Noble, John, Ca. 1967; affiliation: Business Administration (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/59)
  - Nockleby, John, 1975-1976; affiliation: ASUM President (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/60)
  - Noel, Alexander, 1977; affiliation: Assistant to UM Dean of Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/61)
  - Noel, Leah, 1973; affiliation: Coordinator of Events (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/62)
  - Nord, Ron, 1969-1974; affiliation: Athletics (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/63)
  - Norton, Robert Lee, 1965-1966; affiliation: Journalism (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/64)
  - Nye, Mika, ca. late 1960s; affiliation: Foreign Languages (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/65)
  - O'Brien, Mary Carlson, ca. 1970; affiliation: English (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/66)
  - O'Connell, Peggy, 1975; affiliation: Montana Repertory Theater (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/67)
  - O'Connor, Carrol, 1973, 1982; affiliation: Alumni (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/68)
  - O'Gara, Bart W., 1971-1976; affiliation: Forestry, Zoology, Wildlife Biology (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/69)
  - O'Rouke, Peter, 1975-1976; affiliation: Drama (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/70)
  - Oakland, Lloyd Dr., 1952-1968; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/71)
  - Odegard, Peter H., 1966; affiliation: Honorary Doctoral Degree (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/72)
  - Olsen, Arnold, 1967-1969; affiliation: Guest Speaker (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/73)
  - Olsen, Gerry, 1975; affiliation: Center for Continuing Education (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/74)
  - Olson, Barbara, 1974-1977; affiliation: Pharmacy (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/75)
  - Olson, Jock Roger Dr., 1967; affiliation: Speech Pathology (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/76)
  - Olufs, Dick W., 1981; affiliation: Political Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/77)
  - Ostby, Raymond, 1973; affiliation: Accounting (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/78)
  - Ouse, Kathryne E., 1972; affiliation: Military Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/79)
  - Overmyer, Wernon Dr., 1966-1967; affiliation: Music (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/80)
  - Owen, James Dr., 1967; affiliation: Speech Communication (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/81)
  - Pace, R. Wayne, Dr., 1966-1972; affiliation: Speech Communication (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/82)
  - Palmer, William R., 1966; affiliation: Assistant business manager and assistant controller (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/83)
  - Pantzer, Robert T., 1969-1974; affiliation: President (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/84)
  - Pantzer, Robert T., 1966-1973; affiliation: President (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/85)
  - Pantzer, Robert T., 1970-1975; affiliation: President (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/86)
  - Pantzer, Robert T., 1969-1974; affiliation: President (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/87)
  - Papousek, Elizabeth M., ca. late 1960s; affiliation: Mathematics (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/88)
  - Park, Thae Soo, ca. late 1960s; affiliation: Business and Economic Research (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/89)
  - Parrott, Tim, 1972; affiliation: UC Program Coordinator (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/90)
  - Parsons, Neil, 1971, 1973; affiliation: Art (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/91)
  - Pashley, Walter A. Jr., 1968-1972; affiliation: Military Science (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/92)
  - Patent, Dorothy Dr., 1975-1976; affiliation: Biology (Box-folder Series 3 - 4/93)